Guide to the Francis Warrington Dawson Family Papers, 1386-1963, bulk 1859-1950 RL.10147
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1859-1963 and undated
  - Phillipps, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1922-1936 (Box 20)
  - Pichon, S. to Sharp, William, 1919 (Box 20)
  - Pié, Lucille de to Aunt Zay, undated (Box 20)
  - Pié, Lucille de to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 20)
  - Pilkington Bros. Limited to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 20)
  - Pinckney, R. L. to Morgan, Sarah, 1891 (Box 20)
  - Pineau, [?] to Dawson, Warrington, 1938 (Box 20)
  - Pingaud, A. to Dawson, Warrington, 1928 (Box 20)
  - Pinker, James to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1922 (Box 20)
  - Piper, Alexander to Ford, Stanley, 1933 (Box 20)
  - Pitts, Elizabeth to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 20)
  - Pizzarelle, Joseph to [?], 1922 (Box 20)
  - Plumon, E. to Dawson, Warrington, 1929 (Box 20)
  - Plymonth to Dawson, Warrington, 1912-1939 (Box 20)
  - Poincaré, R. to Roosevelt, Theodore, 1918 (Box 20)
  - Polland, Harold to Latham, [?], undated (Box 20)
  - Pollard, A. W. to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 20)
  - Pollard, Ernest to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 20)
  - Polonowski, M. to Dawson, Warrington, 1948-1952 (Box 20)
  - Pose, Ellen to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 20)
  - Potts, Allen to Dawson, Warrington, 1920 (Box 20)
  - Pougeuf, H. to Dawson, Warrington, 1922 (Box 20)
  - Pouquet, Jon to Dawson, Warrington and [?], 1930 and undated (Box 20)
  - Pouzoulet-Christol, Antoine to [?], 1932 (Box 20)
  - Powell, John to Dawson, Warrington, 1908-1932 (Box 20)
  - Price, L. to Dawson, Warrington, 1910 (Box 20)
  - Price, Thomas to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 20)
  - Prince, Albert to Dawson, Warrington, 1919 (Box 20)
  - Prince, Walter F. to [?], 1933 (Box 20)
  - Pringle, B. to Dawson, Warrington, 1909-1935 (Box 20)
  - Pringle, Billy to Dawson, Warrington, 1925 (Box 20)
  - Pringle, Helen to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 20)
  - Proctor, Herbert to Bull, [?], 1914 (Box 20)
  - Proctor, Herbert to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 20)
  - Putnam, Herbert to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 20)
  - Rabago, Casa to Dawson, Warrington, 1938 (Box 20)
  - Rainer, Pinkie to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 20)
  - Rainer, Susie to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 20)
  - Randall, James to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 20)
  - Randall, James to Morgan, Sarah, 1896 (Box 20)
  - Randolph, Margaret to various, 1930-1931 (Box 20)
  - Randolph-Stevenson, R. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 20)
  - Ranjard, M. to Dawson, Warrington, 1939 (Box 20)
  - Ransom, L. A. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 20)
  - Ravenel, Beatrice to Dawson, Warrington, 1928 (Box 20)
  - Ravenel, Daniel to Dawson, F. W., 1883 (Box 20)
  - Ray, Guy to Dawson, Warrington, 1927-1928 (Box 20)
  - Rebaud, Jules to [?], 1919 (Box 20)
  - Recteur, Pierre le to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 20)
  - Reed, Robert to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1931 (Box 20)
  - Reeks, Henry to [?], 1905 (Box 20)
  - Reeks, Joseph to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 20)
  - Reingpach, P. to [?], 1932 (Box 20)
  - Reish, J. W. to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 20)
  - Réjou to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 20)
  - Rénald, Jean to Dawson, Warrington, 1935 (Box 20)
  - Renard, Robert to Dawson, Warrington, 1928-1933 (Box 20)
  - Reopell, C. A. to Thompson, Vance, 1922 (Box 20)
  - Resco, Micheline to Dawson, Warrington, 1953 (Box 20)
  - Reusselaer, Florence van to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 20)
  - Rice, J. G. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 20)
  - Rich, E. G. to Dawson, Warrington, 1923 (Box 20)
  - Richard, Gerault to [?], 1931 (Box 20)
  - Richard, Pierre to Dawson, Warrington, 1939 (Box 20)
  - Richardson, H. W. to various, 1888-1889 (Box 20)
  - Richardson, John to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 20)
  - Richardson, P. to Dawson, Warrington, 1923 (Box 20)
  - Richardson, [?] to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 20)
  - Riddle, J. W. to Dawson, Warrington, 1911 and undated (Box 20)
  - Riordan, R. to [?], 1894 (Box 20)
  - Riou, Yvette to Dawson, Warrington, 1929 (Box 20)
  - Rivet, P. to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 20)
  - Rivet, P. to [?], 1930-1932 (Box 20)
  - Rivet, W. to Dawson, Warrington, 1929 (Box 20)
  - Roach, William to Armstrong, James, 1889 (Box 21)
  - Roany, Comtesse de to Dawson, Warrington, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Roany, X. de to Dawson, Warrington, 1939 (Box 21)
  - Roberts, Elmer to Dawson, Warrington, 1918-1929 (Box 21)
  - Robertson, James to Dawson, Warrington, 1958-1959 (Box 21)
  - Robinson, Corinne to Barry, Ethel, undated (Box 21)
  - Robinson, Corinne to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1932 (Box 21)
  - Robinson, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 21)
  - Rochambeau, [?] de to [?], 1931-1933 (Box 21)
  - Rochs, Jules to [?], 1920 (Box 21)
  - Rockefeller, John D. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1932 (Box 21)
  - Rodin, Auguste to Dawson, Warrington, 1913-1914 (Box 21)
  - Roeder, Ralph to Bayard, [?], 1912 (Box 21)
  - Rogerie, Bourde de la to [?], 1931 (Box 21)
  - Rogers, James to Edge, Walter, 1931 (Box 21)
  - Rogers, [?] to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 21)
  - Rohan, V. to Dawson, Warrington, 1911-1926 and undated (Box 21)
  - Rohan-Chabut, [?] to [?], 1932 and undated (Box 21)
  - Romain-Desfrossés, C. to various, 1931-1932 (Box 21)
  - Romain-Desfrossés, C. to [?], 1930 and undated (Box 21)
  - Romano, Roger to Dawson, Warrington, 1939 and undated (Box 21)
  - Romeike, Albert to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 21)
  - Romeike, Henry to Nagel, Agnes, 1947 (Box 21)
  - Roosevelt, Archie to various, 1921-1922 (Box 21)
  - Roosevelt, Archie to Dawson, Warrington, 1909-1945 (Box 21)
  - Roosevelt, Belle to Dawson, Warrinton, 1945-1946 (Box 21)
  - Roosevelt, Edith to Dawson, Warrington, 1928 (Box 21)
  - Roosevelt, Ethel to Dawson, Warrington, 1910 (Box 21)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor to Dawson, Warrington, 1945-1946 (Box 21)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932-1936 (Box 21)
  - Roosevelt, Grace to Dawson, Warrington, 1920s (Box 21)
  - Roosevelt, Kermit to Dawson, Warrington, 1909-1939; 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Roosevelt, Mary to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 21)
  - Roosevelt, Nicholas to Dawson, Warrington, 1914-1931 and undated (Box 21)
  - Roosevelt, Quentin to Dawson, Warrington, 1914 and undated (Box 21)
  - Roosevelt, T. to Dawson, Warrington, 1909 (Box 21)
    Includes solely telegrams
  - Roosevelt, Theodore to Dawson, Warrington, 1909-1921; 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Rose, Jennie to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 21)
  - Rosel, L. du to [?], 1930 (Box 21)
  - Rosen, E. K. to Dawson, Warrington, 1912-1922 (Box 21)
  - Rosenbaum, [?] to Nagel, Agnes, 1948 (Box 21)
  - Rostand, Jean to [?], 1954 (Box 21)
  - Rostang, Pierre de to [?], 1931 (Box 21)
  - Rougeuf, F. to Dawson, Warrington, 1929 (Box 21)
  - Roustan, D. to Laurka, Mme, 1923 (Box 21)
  - Rouvezrol, Lucien to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 21)
  - Roy, Paule to [?], 1947 (Box 21)
  - Ruechs, Marcel to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 21)
  - Ruffin, Y. to Dawson, Warrington, 1947 (Box 21)
  - Russell, Antoinette to various, 1933-1935 (Box 21)
  - Russell, W. P. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 21)
  - Rutledge, Benjamin to Smith, H., 1890 (Box 21)
  - Ryden, George to Goodwin, W. A. R., 1931 (Box 21)
  - Sackett, M. to [?], 1938 (Box 21)
  - Saffroy, Henri to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 21)
  - Saffroy, Henri to [?], 1931 (Box 21)
  - Saint Georges, A. Renard de to [?], 1946 (Box 21)
  - Salignac Fénelon, Vicomtesse de to [?], 1932-1935 (Box 21)
  - Sands, Oliver to Trustees, 1931 (Box 21)
  - Savelle, Max to Dawson, Warrington, 1928-1932 (Box 21)
  - Scalvini, Martina to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 21)
  - Schepeko, Marie to Dawson, Warrinton, 1946-1947 (Box 21)
  - Scherdlin, E. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 21)
  - Schirmer, C. D. to Dawson, Warrington, 1927-1933 (Box 21)
  - Schneebeli, H. to [?], 1932 (Box 21)
  - Schoellkoff, Walter to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 21)
  - Schroeder, H. L. to Dawson, Warrington, 1948-1952 and undated (Box 22)
  - Schuler, Eric to Dawson, Warrington, 1917 (Box 22)
  - Schwab, Arnold to Dawson, Warrington, 1954-1962 (Box 22)
  - Scott, E. A. to various, 1889 (Box 22)
  - Scott, Leroy to Dawson, Warrington, 1917 (Box 22)
  - Scott, Louise to Dawson, Warrington, 1920 and undated (Box 22)
  - Scribner, Charles to Dawson, Warrington, 1910 (Box 22)
  - Secoutl, Georges to [?], 1929 (Box 22)
  - Segonne, Lilian to various, 1930-1932 (Box 22)
  - Segonne, Lilian to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1932 and undated (Box 22)
  - Seiwell, Don to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 22)
  - Selons, Frederick to Dawson, Warrington, 1910-1913 (Box 22)
  - Senter, Mark to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 22)
  - Septaus, Yvonne to [?], 1932 (Box 22)
  - Serey, Charles to Dawson, Warrington, 1914 (Box 22)
  - Shafeldt, Margaret to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 22)
  - Sharkey, Joseph to Dawson, Warrington, 1929-1932 (Box 22)
  - Sharp, George to various, 1930-1931 (Box 22)
  - Sharp, George to Dawson, Warrington, 1922-1945 and undated (Box 22)
  - Sharp, Hallie Clough to Dawson, Warrington, 1919-1933 and undated (Box 22)
  - Sharp, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1922 and undated (Box 22)
  - Sharp, William to various, 1915-1920 (Box 22)
  - Shaw, Thomas to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 22)
  - Shepperd, J. C. to Dawson, F. W., 1886-1887 (Box 22)
  - Shepherd, Miriam to Dawson, Warrington, 1924 (Box 22)
  - Shepherd, Pinkie to [?], 1889 (Box 22)
  - Shepherd, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 22)
  - Shields, William to [?], 1885 (Box 22)
  - Shurtleff, Harold to Swem, E. G., 1932 (Box 22)
  - Shurtleff, Harold to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1937 (Box 22)
  - Siegfried, André to Dawson, Warrington, 1947-1951 (Box 22)
  - Siegfried, André to [?], 1930 (Box 22)
  - Siegling, Rudolph to Morgan, Sarah, 1891 (Box 22)
  - Sillac, M. de to [?], 1930 (Box 22)
  - Simms, Phil to Dawson, Warrington, 1909-1913 (Box 22)
  - Simmons, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1923 (Box 22)
  - Simon, Samy to Dawson, Warrington, 1949 (Box 22)
  - Simonds, Andrew to [?], 1889 (Box 22)
  - Simonds, Sallie to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 22)
  - Simons, Elizabeth to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 and undated (Box 22)
  - Sims, Olga to Dawson, Warrington, 1922 (Box 22)
  - Singer, Fred to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 22)
  - Singleton, Ann to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 22)
  - Sloan, P. to [?], 1888 (Box 22)
  - Small, Maynard, & Co. to Dawson, Warrington, 1910 (Box 22)
  - Small, R. S. to Barry, Herbert, 1926 (Box 22)
  - Smith, Constance to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 22)
  - Smith, George to Dawson, Warrington, 1909-1910 (Box 22)
  - Smith, Henry to Morgan, Sarah, 1889-1905 (Box 22)
  - Smith, Kate to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 22)
  - Smith, Mary to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 22)
  - Smith, Richard to various, 1932 (Box 22)
  - Smith, Wabell to Dawson, Warrington, 1912 (Box 22)
  - Smith, William to various, 1931 (Box 22)
  - Smyth, Ellison to Barry, Stuyvesant, 1930 (Box 22)
  - Smyth, J. A. to [?], 1898 (Box 22)
  - Smyth, Robert to Dawson, F. W., 1895 (Box 22)
  - Snell, A. to Dawson, Warrington, 1913 (Box 23)
  - Snow, George to Dawson, Warrington, 1937 (Box 23)
  - Snowden, M. to Barry, Stuyvesant, 1930-1931 (Box 23)
  - Sours, P. E. to Dawson, Warrington, 1947 (Box 23)
  - Spaur, D. R. to various, 1931-1935 and undated (Box 23)
  - Spedon, S. M. to Dawson, Warrington, 1924-1925 (Box 23)
  - Spofford, E. to Dawson, Warrington, 1912 (Box 23)
  - Spotswood, Dandridge to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 23)
  - Sprague, Ernest to Goodwin, W. A. R., 1931 (Box 23)
  - Sprigg, S. B. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 23)
  - Standing, A. W. to various, 1932 (Box 23)
  - Stanton, Theodore to Dawson, Warrington, 1919 (Box 23)
  - Starr, Homer to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 23)
  - Starr, W. W. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 23)
  - Steele, Frank to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 23)
  - Stein, Guy to [?], 1932 (Box 23)
  - Sterling, F. to Dawson, Warrington, 1920-1927 (Box 23)
  - Stevens, Albert to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 23)
  - Stevenson, Daisy to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 23)
  - Steward, J. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 and undated (Box 23)
  - Stimson, Henry to Borah, William, 1932 (Box 23)
  - Stoller, Alexander to [?], 1932 (Box 23)
  - Storms, Alice to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 23)
  - Stoney, Louisa to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 23)
  - Stoney, Sam to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 and undated (Box 23)
  - Stout, Francis to Dawson, F. W., 1889 (Box 23)
  - Straus, Jesse to Dawson, Warrington, 1934 (Box 23)
  - Straus, Robert to Dawson, Warrington, 1936 (Box 23)
  - Street, George A. to Dawson, Warrington, 1911 (Box 23)
  - Strohl, Doyen to [?], 1931 (Box 23)
  - Stubbs, T. J. to [?], 1932 (Box 23)
  - Sturgis, Russell to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 23)
  - Stutton, N. E. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 23)
  - Sullivan, Harriet to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1922 (Box 23)
  - Sumner, Edward to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 23)
  - Surbled, D. to [?], 1912 (Box 23)
  - Swem, E. G. to various, 1930-1934 (Box 23)
  - Swital, Chet to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 23)
  - Symington, W. to Dawson, F. W., 1885 (Box 23)
  - Tabord, G. M. to Daladier, 1938 (Box 23)
  - Talbird, Thomas to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 23)
  - Taylor, Olivia to Goodwin, W. A. R., 1931 (Box 23)
  - Taylor, Robert to Dawson, Warrington, 1944-1945 (Box 23)
  - Taylor, Virginia to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 23)
  - Thaw, Benjamin to various, 1930 (Box 23)
  - Thaw, Benjamin to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1931 (Box 23)
  - Thébaud, Hewlett to Dawson, Warrington, 1934 (Box 23)
  - Thèbes, A. de to [?], undated (Box 23)
  - Thezac, François de to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 23)
  - Thibaud, Robert to Ledoux, Carlos, 1939 (Box 23)
  - Thomas, Bessie to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 23)
  - Thomas, J. to [?], Henry, 1888 (Box 23)
  - Thomas, Marselle to [?], 1946-1948 (Box 23)
  - Thomas, W. M. to Morgan, Sarah, 1892 (Box 23)
  - Thompson, C. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 23)
  - Thompson, Hugh S. to Dawson, F. W., 1879-1889 and undated (Box 23)
  - Thompson, Hugh S. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 23)
  - Thompson, Lillian to Dawson, Warrington, 1922-1925 (Box 23)
  - Thompson, R. S. to Dawson, Warrington, 1923 (Box 23)
  - Thompson, Ralph to Dawson, Warrington, 1909 (Box 23)
  - Thompson, Sydney to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 23)
  - Thompson, Tyler to [?], 1940 (Box 23)
  - Thompson, Vance to Dawson, Warrington, 1908-1925?; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Thomson, Walter to Sharp, Hallie Clough, 1930 (Box 23)
  - Thornhill, T. J. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 23)
  - Thring, Herbert to Dawson, Warrington and [?], 1922 (Box 23)
  - Tillman, Benjamin to Dawson, F. W., 1886-1888 (Box 23)
  - Tinker, Edward to Dawson, Warrington, 1933 (Box 23)
  - Tipton, Charles to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 23)
  - Todd, A. S. to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 23)
  - Tong, Jocelyn to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 23)
  - Tonnochy, Eva to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 23)
  - Tournon, Paul to Dawson, Warrington, 1951-1952 (Box 23)
  - Townsend, James to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 23)
  - Trenholm, W. L. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 23)
  - Tricoglou, J. G. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 and undated (Box 23)
  - Trotter, Gerard to various, 1930-1935 (Box 23)
  - Tuck, Edward to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 23)
  - Tuck, S. Pinkney to Dawson, Warrington, 1933 (Box 24)
  - Tupper, Samuel to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 24)
  - Tyler, Ryan to Dawson, Warrington, 1929 (Box 24)
  - Uganda Royalty to various, 1909 (Box 24)
  - Usher, V. J. to Dawson, Warrington, 1925 (Box 24)
  - Vacaresco, Hélène to [?], undated (Box 24)
  - Vail, R. W. to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1927 (Box 24)
  - Vail, Samuel to Dawson, Warrington, 1909-1910 (Box 24)
  - Valdes, Elizabeth to Dawson, Warrington, 1933-1939 (Box 24)
  - Valentine, Edward to Dawson, Warrington, 1912 (Box 24)
  - Vanderbilt, Reginald to Barry, Ethel, 1932 (Box 24)
  - Van Sickle, John to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1931 (Box 24)
  - Vauquelin, Pierre to [?], 1931 (Box 24)
  - Veit, Sidney to Dawson, Warrington, 1929 (Box 24)
  - Vermeren, Emile to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 24)
  - Very, G. to [?], 1931 (Box 24)
  - Vezey, H. to Dawson, Warrington, 1904 (Box 24)
  - Viard, Henri to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 24)
  - Vigue, Renée Rouault de la to [?], 1931 (Box 24)
  - Vilas, William to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 24)
  - Villemandy, Henri de to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 24)
  - Virkus, Frederick to Dawson, Warrington, 1929-1933 (Box 24)
  - Visanska, J. M. to Dawson, Warrington, 1910 (Box 24)
  - Vitrolles to [?], 1931 (Box 24)
  - Vivien, Joseph du to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 24)
  - Vivielle, J. to [?], 1931 (Box 24)
  - Voorhis, Harold to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1932 (Box 24)
  - Vredenburgh, John van Vorst to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 24)
  - Wagner, George to Morgan, Sarah, 1891 (Box 24)
  - Wainwright, J. M. to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 24)
  - Walker, Evans, & Cogswell Co. to Dawson, Warrington, 1927-1934 (Box 24)
  - Walker, J. to Morgan, Sarah, 1874 (Box 24)
  - Wall, Jeannette to Morgan, Sarah, 1898 (Box 24)
  - Wallace, Helen M. to Dawson, Warrington, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Wallace, Hugh to Dawson, Warrington, 1922-1930 (Box 24)
  - Wallace, Mildred to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1933 (Box 24)
  - Wallace, Renée to Dawson, Warrington, 1913 (Box 24)
  - Wallace, W. H. to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 24)
  - Walsh, Patrick to Dawson, F. W., 1887-1889 (Box 24)
  - Ward, E. S. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 24)
  - Ward, Herbert to [?], 1889-1891 (Box 24)
  - Warden, W. L. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 24)
  - Waring, T. R. to Dawson Trust, 1952 (Box 24)
  - Washington, Martha to Morgan, Sarah, 1889-1905 (Box 24)
  - Washington, Martha to Dawson, Warrington, 1926 (Box 24)
  - Watson, D. to Dawson, Warrington, 1906-1909 (Box 24)
  - Watson, J. H. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 24)
  - Watson, G. Morgan to Morgan, Sarah, 1873-1878 (Box 24)
  - Watson, Margaret to Dawson, Warrington, 1915 (Box 24)
  - Watterson, Henry to [?], 1887 (Box 24)
  - Way, Katharine to Dawson, Warrington, 1911 (Box 24)
  - Webber, Mabel to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 24)
  - Webbey, Charles to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 24)
  - Weber, J. L. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 24)
  - Webster, George to Massie, Hughes, 1910 (Box 24)
  - Weddell, Alexander to various, 1930 (Box 24)
  - Weddell, Alexander to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 24)
  - Weeley, Jean to Dawson, Warrington?, 1930-1933 (Box 24)
  - Weilland, Jean to Dawson, Warrington, 1939 (Box 24)
  - Weisenberg, Leslie to Cocke, Jack, 1930 (Box 24)
  - Weisenberg, Leslie to various, 1930-1932 (Box 24)
  - Weisenberg, Leslie to Dawson, Warrington, 1926-1935 (Box 24)
  - Weldon, F. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 24)
  - Welen, J. L. to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 24)
  - Well, Edward to Dawson, F. W., 1889 (Box 24)
  - Wellborn, Mary to Dawson, Warrinton, 1931-1932 (Box 24)
  - Wells, Henry to [?], 1888 (Box 24)
  - Welson, Harry to Dawson, Warrington, 1909 (Box 24)
  - Werlich, McCeney to Dawson, Warrington, 1934-1935 (Box 24)
  - West, James E. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 24)
  - Weston, F. H. to [?], 1889 (Box 24)
  - Wheeler, Everett to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 24)
  - Wheeler, Nina to [?], 1889 (Box 24)
  - White, Bernard to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 24)
  - White, Bernard to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 24)
  - White, Edwin to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 24)
  - White, F. S. to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 24)
  - White, George to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 24)
  - White, Henry to Dawson, Warrington, 1909-1910 (Box 24)
  - White, Thomas to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 24)
  - Whitehead, Helen to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 24)
  - Whitehouse, Sheldon to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1927 (Box 25)
  - Whitford, Reid to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 25)
  - Whitner, B. to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 25)
  - Whitney, Edward to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 25)
  - Whitney, E. G. to [?], 1862-1863 (Box 25)
  - Whitney, W. C. to Dawson, F. W., undated (Box 25)
  - Wicker, Francis to Dawson, Warrington, 1917 (Box 25)
  - Wilcox, John to [?], 1889 (Box 25)
  - Wilford, Belle to Dawson, Warrington, 1926 (Box 25)
  - Willem van Loon, Hendrik to Author's Guild, 1939 (Box 25)
  - Williams, A. B. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 25)
  - Williams, A. B. to Courseway, W. A., 1887 (Box 25)
  - Williams, Chas to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 25)
  - Williams, Clayton to Dawson, Warrington, 1935 (Box 25)
  - Williams, John L. B. to Dawson, Warrington, 1934-1937 (Box 25)
  - Williams, J. S. to various, 1935 (Box 25)
  - Williams, Tom to Dawson, Warrington, 1920 (Box 25)
  - Williamson, Harold to various, 1931-1934 (Box 25)
  - Williamson, Harold to Dawson, Warrington, 1929-1935 (Box 25)
  - Willis, E. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 25)
  - Willis, Eliza to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 25)
  - Willis, J. E. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 25)
  - Wills, Louis A. to Dawson, Riordan, 1880 (Box 25)
  - Willson, B. to Dawson, Warrington, 1926-1935 (Box 25)
  - Willson, Ida to Dawson, Warrington, 1935 (Box 25)
  - Wilson, Benjamin H. to Dawson, F. W., 1872 (Box 25)
  - Wilson, Edith to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 25)
  - Wilson, H. L. to Dawson, Warrington, 1910 (Box 25)
  - Wilson, Huntington to Dawson, Warrington, 1915 (Box 25)
  - Wilson, Warden to Dawson, Warrington, 1929 (Box 25)
  - Wilson, Woodrow to Sharp, William, 1914 (Box 25)
  - Wilt, A. & Sons to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 25)
  - Winterhalden, Mathie to Dawson, Warrington, 1920 (Box 25)
  - Wofford, John to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 25)
  - Wold, Ansel to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 25)
  - Wood, John C. to various, 1931 (Box 25)
  - Wood, John R. to Dawson, Warrington, 1941 (Box 25)
  - Woods, Arthur to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1932 (Box 25)
  - Woodward, S. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 25)
  - Worthing, Henry to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 25)
  - Wragg, Eleanor to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 25)
  - Wrenson, Thad to Burger, Karl, 1939 (Box 25)
  - Wright, Gustin to Dawson, Warrington, 1929 (Box 25)
  - Wylie, O. A. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 25)
  - Yindrock, F. N. to various, 1927-1933 (Box 25)
  - York, Ruth to Dawson, Warrington, 1925 (Box 25)
  - Yorke-Blanchot, Mme to [?], 1931 (Box 25)
  - Young, Henry E. to [?], 1892 (Box 25)
  - Young, S. Jane to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 25)
  - [?], Harvie to Dawson, Warrington, 1922 (Box 25)
  - [?], Howard to Dawson, Warrington, 1909 (Box 25)
    Solely telegrams
  - [?], Laurie to Dawson, Warrington, 1923-1925 (Box 25)
  - [?], "Little Mary" to Dawson, Warrington, 1912 (Box 25)
  - [?], Lucile to Morgan, Sarah, 1903 (Box 25)
  - [?], Lucile to Dawson, Warrington, 1917 (Box 25)
  - [?], Miriam to [?], 1864-1898 and undated (Box 25)
    A researcher has identified Miriam as Miriam Morgan Dupre, sister of Sarah Morgan Dawson. The first letter, on green paper, without a salutation, is to James Morris Morgan, brother of Miriam and Sarah. He was in the Confederate Navy. He was the only brother in the War left alive by then. Other letters are to Sarah Morgan Dawson, whose family nickname was Zay.
  - [?], Quentin to Dawson, Warrington, 1909 (Box 25)
  - [?] Russell to Dawson, Warrington, 1922 (Box 25)
  - General Correspondence, 1860-1912 (Box 26)
  - General Correspondence, 1913-1926 (Box 27)
  - General correspondence, 1927-1930 (Box 28)
  - General correspondence, 1931 (Box 29)
  - General correspondence, 1932-1935 (Box 30)
  - General correspondence, 1936-1963 and undated (Box 31)
  - General Telegrams, 1909; 1 folders (Box 31)
  - Miscellaneous Envelopes, various; 2 folders (Box 31 and 99)
  - Letterpress books of F.W. Dawson I, 1879-1887
    - I, 1879-1884 (Box 75)
    - II, 1884-1887 (Box 75)
  - Diplomatic Papers, 2 boxes